{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":180,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":2,"width":740,"height":555,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_273","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_273","roles":{}},{"id":"si34125","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34121","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34017","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"              Welcome to the CSAM Matching Game       Match the phishing term with its definition and ‘Submit’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34024","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34028","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34048","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34052","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34073","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Smishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34094","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Search Engine Phishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34471","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34475","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Spear Phishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34493","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Whaling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34507","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34511","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Catphishing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34035","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Column 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34039","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34058","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34062","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Not random - targeting one user ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34062ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Not random - targeting one user","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34083","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Targets ‘C’ titles (CEO, CFO, CIO, etc.) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34083ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targets ‘C’ titles (CEO, CFO, CIO, etc.)","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34100","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34104","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Phishing over the phone (voice) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34104ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Phishing over the phone (voice)","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34519","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34523","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Targets dating sites and social media ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34523ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targets dating sites and social media","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34534","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Using SMS (texting) alerts  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34534ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Using SMS (texting) alerts ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34541","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Creating a fake webpage ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34545ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Creating a fake webpage","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si34129","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34146","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34159","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34171","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34201","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34213","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34230","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34243","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33964q0","for":"Slide33964q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34109","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34113","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34117","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33964","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_273","si34017","si34062","si34083","si34104","si34523","si34534","si34545","si34129","si34146","si34159","si34171","si34188","si34201","si34213","si34230","si34243","si34117"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33964"},"question":{"interactionId":"33980","quizId":458,"title":"Matching","text":"              Welcome to the CSAM Matching Game\r\r     Match the phishing term with its definition and ‘Submit’\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_278","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_280","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_280","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34584","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34588","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attempts: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34592","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34596","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si34600","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"CSAM Phishing Game","class":"project","title":"CSAM Phishing Game","children":["Slide33964","Slide6038"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide33964q0"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":10,"passScore":8}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide33964","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 2"}]}